http://www.poisonweb.com/privacy

Overview
This web site is powered by products and services from BubbleUp LLC. (BubbleUp). BubbleUp's privacy policy is below.
Privacy Statement for BubbleUp.
BubbleUp has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for BubbleUp and all other Web sites powered by BubbleUp.
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.
BubbleUp uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart (if present) and to keep track of your membership status on the Web site. We use cookies to save your authenticated session ID so you don't have to re-enter password each time you visit our site.
Our registration form requires users to give us contact information (could include name and e-mail address and demographic information like zip code). The contact information is used to contact you when necessary and may be shared with other select companies. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. We do not share mailing address, credit card, or any personally identifiable information with other companies. Demographic and profile data are used only for personalized Web content and statistical information and are not shared with other companies except in ways that do not personally identify our users.
This site may contain links to other sites. BubbleUp is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We place advertising on our site that originates from third party advertisers and/or advertising agencies. Even though these advertisements are embedded in our Web site, cookies may be assigned by the advertisers themselves. BubbleUp does not control those cookies.
This site may use an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (e-mail address) and financial information (credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send our customer's orders and information about our company and about companies we choose. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary and may be shared with other select companies who want to contact the user. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial and contact information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services and may be shared with companies that help us operate our site, such as the credit card companies that we use.
BubbleUp may run contests on this site in which we ask visitors for contact information (e-mail address) and demographic information (zip code). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and about companies we choose. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary and may be shared with other select companies who want to contact the user. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We may share your contact and demographic information with the contest prize providers.
On some websites BubbleUp provides online ticketing to venues in which we ask customers for contact information (e-mail address and mailing and billing addresses). BubbleUp provides your contact information to the venues, performers and/or promoters of the events for which you purchase tickets. By purchasing tickets, you acknowledge that BubbleUp has no control over and is not responsible for the privacy policies of those venues, performers or promoters or their subsequent use of your contact information.
In addition, BubbleUp collects and stores statistics and other information about the online activities of our users on an aggregated (collected) basis. For example, we track the number of people who view each page, the order in which pages are viewed, and other information to learn which features are the most popular and to refine our design and marketing efforts.
You agree that we may assign, sell, license or otherwise transfer to a third party your information in connection with an assignment, sale, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of all or substantially all of the assets or capital stock of BubbleUp or its affiliated entities.
Public Forums
Some sites may have chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Nowhere we store your passwords unencrypted, your credit card information is not stored anywhere on our servers, and transactions are enacted using SSL encryption through PCI standard compliant gateway. We may be required to release personal information about you as a result of a lawsuit or subpoena or as immediately necessary to protect our rights or the rights and safety of others. Additionally, "perfect security" does not exist on the internet.
Children's Guidelines
BubbleUp strongly encourages parents and guardians to supervise their children's online activities and to consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools also can prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other personally identifiable information without parental permission. Tickets for sale are intended for purchase by adults. By making a purchase on the site, you agree that you are at least 13 years of age. Although the BubbleUp site is not directed to children under the age of 13, BubbleUp does
NOT collect online contact information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.
NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.
NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.
NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.
NOT entice children under the age of 13 by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This site gives users the option of removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
Simply update your email preferences on the site.
